thank you very much thank oh thank you I
appreciate it thank you thank you very
much thank you welcome to the night of
show I am Larry Larry Larry
Larry okay now before we get
going last night was the Super Bowl
congratulations Patriots I know you won
right congrat no it's okay no I'm a
Seahawks fan and um I really slam the
Pats on Thursday show I mean I hit your
team like wiked
hard I did and then I put this thing
online if the Patriots win I will eat a
bowl of whatever you call it New England
clam
chower there you
go yeah man of my
work I am a man of my word I got a big
bowl of New England Glam chatter it's
actually looks pretty good I if I need
any oyster crackers or anything all
right okay let's just do
this very good that's not cheating
Patriots fans I just deflated the size
of the bowl so it's easier to gra
bam yeah
B
horrible oh my
God Wicked hide Wicked hide okay now the
only thing more depressing than the game
last night was the commercials I
couldn't grow up because I died from an
accident
Jesus I just wanted to watch a football
game you know I didn't know I had to
prepare eulogy for for a
child I mean man I was already feeling
crappy enough about eating my famous
seven layer corn torto double dip bacon
deep fried sour cream stuff crust Panini
trademark don't act like it was just me
you guys had your button pop by halftime
too right in fact on Super Bowl Sunday
Americans consumed roughly 1.25 billion
chicken wings 11.2 million pounds of
potato chips and 49.2 million cases of
beer that's right
suck on that Third World USA USA USA USA
USA it's actually it's actually not the
time to chant
there okay America I think it's time for
an intervention you
fat okay seriously no seriously Gallup
just released the Obesity stats for 2014
and the numbers spiked to
27.7% nearly a third of our country is
obese
now I'm not going to make you know no no
I'm not going to make a joke about that
no no no the last thing we should be
doing is making font of fat people right
now in this time of obvious crisis and I
condemn anyone out there making cheap
fat jokes a lot of people are upset at
Michael Moore for throwing shade at
snipers but in all fairness he throws
shadeed on almost everything in his
immediate
vicinity I know I'm sorry okay everyone
can make a mistake once all right I mean
Top Gun taught us that we need to take
care of our vets because some of our
soldiers age well and some
don't looks like the Ice Man became the
ice cream
man okay guilty is charged okay in light
of this new information um I just now
released this statement I am terribly
ashamed of my
comments they were made in a moment of
weakness upon seeing Val Ker's
face he really let himself go but that
is no excuse for me making fun of him I
make no apologies for my statement
regarding Michael Mo Shadow however
that's just
Science Now obesity is clearly a problem
here in the US but what about the rest
of the world Europe's highest court has
ruled that obesity can in certain cases
be considered a disability my eyebrows
are
uphead calm down British Don
Lemon
okay okay okay so so obesity is a
disability in Europe but so is working
in bathing
boom I'm sorry I'm sorry I know I
shouldn't have said that it's not right
okay I've just released an apology to
the British
people I would like to apologize to the
British people that was completely out
of line I still make no apologies for my
statements about Michael Mo Shadow
however that's still just
science science can't be TR what are you
going to do okay so in Europe obesity
has been classified as a disability well
that's not how we play in America the
hospital is instituting a hiring policy
that excludes overweight candidates
overweight Pilots with a BMI of at least
40 or with a neck that's at least 17 in
must be evaluated waitresses can be
fired for gaining more than 7% of their
original body weight overweight women
earn smaller paychecks than average size
women that's that's right um your mama
is so fat okay uh your mama so fat she
suffers from systemic bias in a job
market that marginalizes her just based
on her appearance
[Applause]
oh know how those go um and it doesn't
in there in most of the country you can
still fire someone for being obese and
then when you're unemployed you're
likely to gain more weight making it
harder to find a job it's a vicious Soul
cycle of
Injustice so for actively discriminating
against obese people brings up the
question should obesity be treated as a
civil rights issue now I get it it's
tough being overweight in today's
society magazines television and movies
are full of images of thin people having
good stuff happen to them I mean it's
true even if you go to church you see a
P90X version of Jesus on the
cross
right I mean talk about CrossFit
right am I right bam
sure am I right Christian
ladies okay I'd like to is an apology to
my Christian laters my mockery of Jesus
though accurate was way out of line
unlike the Michael Mo blah blah blah at
all look
okay okay my point is if Jesus looked
like this more galanakis than
cisel okay maybe we wouldn't hear people
in this case a politician finding this
as the cause of Eric Garner's death you
had a 350b person who is resisting
arrest if he had not had asthma and a
heart condition and was so obese that
almost definitely he would not have died
wow wow now look I'm not sure if obesity
is a civil rights issue but I'm sure of
one thing the way we're treating obese
people it ain't right we'll be right
back
hey America follow the nightly show with
Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that stalk